Guide to the Frederick Kuh papers, 1924-1967 MS2109
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Commencement Address-The Significance of Soviet Productive Power, 06/10/1956 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- The Problem OF Peace In Korea, 10/24/1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- The Geneva Conference Of Heads of Government, 07/18/1955-07/23/1955 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- London and Paris Agreements, 09/1954-10/1954 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Austrian State Treaty, 05/15/1955 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- The Southeast Asia Collective Defense Treaty, 01/25/1955 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- The Southeast Asia Collective Defense Treaty Hearing, 11/11/1954 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Japanese Peace Treaty And Other Treaties Relating To Security In The Pacific, 01/10/1952-01/14/1952 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Foreign-Aid Program In Europe, 07/1953 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Factual Campaign Information, 09/12/1956 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Calendar of Business, 01/06/1953 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- The Department of State Bulletin, 11/07/1955 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- The Conferences At Malta And Yalta 1945 (Part I--Galleys 1-434), 03/16/1955 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- The Conferences At Malta And Yalta 1945 (Part II--Galleys 435-834), 03/16/1955 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- In Quest of Peace and Security, 1941-1951 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Report On The Book And Library Program, 07/1953 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Report On The Operations Of The Overseas Book And Library Program, 07/15/1953 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- The Schuman Plan Constituting a European Coal and Steel Community, 04/1951 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Southeast Asia: Critical Area In A Divided World, 06/1955 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Treaties In Force, 10/13/1955 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Der Uranbergbau in der Sowjetzone, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Haben Die Vereinigten Staaten Eine Aussenpolitik?, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
- The Middle East As A Laboratory For Disarmament And Development, 03/09/1957 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Regional Organizations... Europe And The North Atlantic Area, 04/1953 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Treaty of Peace With Japan, 09/08/1951 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- The United States and Germany 1945-1955, 05/1955 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Our Second Chance in Europe What Are We Waiting For?, 04/11/1957 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Turning Point Toward Peace, 10/1955 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- How Not to Run for President, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- To Make A Free World, 01/1955 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- The Leadership We Need and the Leadership We Have, 07/12/1956 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- A Trade And Tariff Policy In The National Interest, 01/1953 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- A Trade And Tariff Policy In the National Interest, 01/1953 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Public Advisory Board For Mutual Security, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
- The Suez Canal: Facts and Figures, 08/15/1956 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Grenzen Der Sowjetmacht, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- The World Today, 01/1955 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- The World Today, 08/08/1955-08/20/1955 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- An Appraisal Of The Cold War, 01/22/1955 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Die gegenwartige Lage und der Kampf um das neue Deatuschland, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- World Economic Survey 1955, 04/27/1956 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Civil Action NO. 2203, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Mutual Defense Assistance Control Act of 1951 (The Battle Act), 1953 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Mutual Defense Assistance Control Act of 1951 (The Battle Act), 1954 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- The Atlantic-Churchill Was Right, 07/1954 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- The Atlantic, 12/1957 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Newspaper clippings-The Eastern Economist, 12/06/1957 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Sunday Star, 01/09/1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Hadassah Newsletter-Home And Country, 01/1941-09/1958 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- New Republic, 01/16/1943-06/24/1957 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Progressive, 01/1962-06/1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Saturday Review, 09/03/1955-11/29/1958 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- The Nation, 06/27/1959-11/01/1964 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 04/24/1952-07/21/1955 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 07/28/1955-05/31/1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 06/07/1956-03/07/1957 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 03/21/1957-12/12/1957 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 01/01/1958-05/08/1958 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 05/15/1958-12/18/1958 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 01/01/1959-10/01/1959 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 10/08/1959-06/01/1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 06/16/1960-01/01/1961 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 01/09/1961-10/12/1961 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 10/19/1961-04/19/1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 05/03/1962-12/20/1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 01/03/1963-07/04/1963 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Foreign Report published by The Economist, 07/18/1963-01/27/1966 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Autobiographical essay by Charles Stainmore, 10/20/1966 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  Charles Stainmore was a pseudonym used by Frederick Kuh. This document is 7 pages long. The file also contains a poem written by Frederick Kuh and some note cards from Ruth Harris with some remembrances of Kuh.
- Memorandum: subject Formosa and President Truman's statement on Formosa (Box 47, Folder 2)
  These documents have been declassified.
- Protocol relative to the treaty respecting Antarctica, 07/18/1963-01/27/1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  This document has been declassified. There is a handwritten note "Re: story of March 10, 1959 (RH) 23 May '74.